[

](https://supervisionassist.com/)

Menu

Privacy Policy
==============

We understand trusting us with your information is a big responsibility. This policy is meant to help you understand what information we collect, why we collect it, and how it will be used. 

_Last updated 4/19/2022  
_

This website is owned and operated by Supervision Assist, LLC (“The Company”). We are committed to protecting the privacy of our members/users while they interact with the content, products and services on Supervision Assist (SA) , this site (the “Site”). This Privacy Policy applies to the Site only. It does not apply to other websites to which we link. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we want you to understand what information we collect about you, how we collect it, how that information is used, and how you can control our disclosure of it. You agree that your use of the Site signifies your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site.

**1) Information Collected**

We collect two types of information from you: i) information that you voluntarily provide to us (e.g. through a voluntary registration process, sign-ups or emails); and ii) information that is derived through automated tracking mechanisms.

Voluntary Registration Information.

In order to fully access this Site, you must first complete the registration process, during which we will collect your personal information. The information will include your name, address, email address, phone number, and other information that may be required by your college/university, faculty supervisor and/or site supervisor. 

By registering with us, you consent to the use and method of disclosure as described in this Privacy Policy.

Voluntary Information for Services and Features 

We also collect personally identifiable information when you choose to use certain other features of the Site, including: i) making CE purchases, ii) consenting to receive email or text messages from supervisors and others involved in your supervision experience, iii) uploading documents used in the supervision process, iv) participating in our forum, blog, and other features of the Site, iv) commenting on articles, and other new services as they are introduced on the site. 

Cookies

Our site uses “cookies” and other tracking technologies. Cookies enable us to serve secure pages to our users without asking them to sign in repeatedly. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. If a user’s system is idle for a defined time, the cookie will expire, forcing the user to sign in again to continue their session. This prevents unauthorized access to the user’s information while they are away from their computer. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the Site.

**2) How We Use Your Information**

SA only uses your personal information for the original purposes it was given. Your personal information will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without your approval at the time of collection.

The Company will not disclose, use, give or sell any personal information to third parties for any purposes other than to your academic institution and site supervisor and clinic in order to deliver services at your request and on your behalf. Further, SA staff reserves the right to contact you regarding matters relevant to the underlying service provided and/or the information collected.

Please note that personally identifiable information is used only to provide you with a more enjoyable, convenient online experience and to help us identify and/or provide information, products or services that may be of interest to you. We use your personally identifiable information to support and enhance your use of the Site and its features, including without limitation: assisting your supervision training experience; providing communication among you your supervisors; and otherwise supporting your use of the Site. 

SA may use your information among other members/users of SA for research and for making improvement to SA. 

**Users who register to use SA as part of their supervision experience are stipulating that their data, journal notes, and other content entered into SA is available and accessible to their academic institutions and site supervisors’ clinics. If you do NOT want your supervision information available to your academic institution or site supervisor’s clinic, then DO NOT use this site.  
**

Also, your information on SA may be used by your academic institution and site supervision clinic for research and making improvements in their supervisory services. 

The Company may transfer information you added into SA in an electronic format to your academic institution or site supervisor clinic at The Company’s sole discretion. 

The Company may disclose Contact Information in special cases where we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our terms and conditions of use or may be causing injury or interference with our rights, property, our customers or anyone who could be harmed by such activities.

WE ARE NOT LIABLE OR RESPONSIBLE FOR THE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE OR OTHER INFORMATION YOU CHOOSE TO SUBMIT IN FORUMS SUCH AS A BULLETIN BOARD, BLOGS, CHAT ROOM OR ANY OTHER PUBLICLY ACCESSIBLE AREA OF THE SITE. 

You will receive notice when your personally identifiable information might be provided to any third party for any reason other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy, and you will have an opportunity to request that we not share such information.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to make improvements in SA website and for research business and administrative purposes. We may also use or share with third parties for any purpose aggregated data that contains no personally identifiable information.

**3) How We Protect Your Information**

We are committed to protecting the information we receive from you. We take appropriate security measures to protect your information against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we maintain appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information and data stored on our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures we have implemented reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

**4) Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information and Preferences**

We provide mechanisms for updating and correcting your personal information for many of our services. You may modify or remove any of your personal information at any time by logging into your account and accessing features such as edit and account.   

**5) Children’s Privacy**

We do not solicit any personal information from children. If you are not 18 or older, you are not authorized to use the Site. 

**6) Disclaimer to Security**

By consenting to the Terms and Conditions of the Site and hence the Privacy Policy, you consent that no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure. We cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you provide to us and you transmit such information to us at your own risk.

**7) Notification of Changes**

SA reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. If at some point in the future, there is a change to our Privacy Policy, unless we obtain your express consent, such change will only apply to information collected after the revised Privacy Policy took effect. Your continued use of the Site indicates your assent to the Privacy Policy as posted.

**8) CONTACT INFORMATION:**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy please contact us.

Supervision Assist   
[\[email protected\]](https://supervisionassist.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)   
888-318-0520

### DOWNLOAD A **FREE EVALUATION TOOL**

Sign up for the Supervision Assist newsletter and we’ll send you a free professional awareness evaluation download right now.

Name 

Email 

Subscribe

© 2024 Supervision Assist, LLC

Thank You. We Received Your Request.
------------------------------------

##### We will call you during your next availability window to discuss your free demo.

##### We look forward to speaking with you!
